Monsters are surging
in the forests of Girtonia.
People are getting hurt.
Philia, my sister, I ask for your guidance.
I can't rely on Prince Julius.
He doesn't care a whit for this kingdom.
If he did, he'd never have sold you—
I was wondering if you've perchance
noticed the ongoing abnormalities.
As I've heard nothing from you,
I thought I might write to you myself.
I hope this missive finds you well...
Is there any point in doing this?
If she's noticed the abnormalities,
surely she would have sent guidance by now.
The fact that she hasn't means...
Big Sister, I hope...
you're not suffering, are you?
Do you have anyone there on your side?
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Episode 4
"Feelings Entrusted"
Quite a number of people are watching.
Sorry to make a spectacle out of it.
My father said it was a good chance
to introduce the people to the our new saint
and opened the event to the public.
I'll admit it's efficient and word
will get around fast, but still...
I don't mind.
Oh, thank goodness. I'm not too late.
Philia.
I'm told of the work you're doing.
I can see bringing you here
was the right decision.
It was worth the fight with my brother.
B-Brother!
Did you have to bring that up now?
Saint Philia!
Everything is in place!
Ah, of course.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Miss Philia!
I leave our kingdom in your capable hands.
They're all such nice people.
Perfectly earnest, with great
love for their kingdom.
They're kind and have generous hearts.
Even though I wasn't born here,
I want to protect these people.
I want to stay the saint of Parnacorta.
I shall begin.
Lives that sprout and grow from the soil...
Lives that fly high into the sky...
Hear and convey my prayer.
Mom, the saint is like a goddess!
Saint Philia is so beautiful!
Let the pillar of protection
grow from the earth
and the purifying light give its love to us.
I swear an oath that as long
as my will remains true,
nothing shall penetrate this barrier.
Great Purification Circle.... activate!
It's finished.
I've found you.
I've found you!
What in the world was that?
Saint Philia!
You did great!
That was great! Just great, Saint Philia!
Saint Philia!
You're wonderful!
Thank you so much!
Isn't the weather just lovely today?
Parnacorta is the picture
of peace and tranquility!
Lena!
Some vegetables! Take them to the saint!
Eggs give you strength!
Take them to the saint!
I made Saint Philia pastries!
Mm...
Take some fruit from our farm!
I knitted this scarf just for her!
Take our latest facial powder to the saint!
I can't carry all this!
I'm back!
You're working again!
Goodness, I told you to at least take
a break while you can't leave the capital.
Just get some rest already.
I'd like to.
I just didn't know what else to do...
You don't have any hobbies or anything?
Not in particular.
That's awful!
Then how about we take a walk?
It's Saint Philia!
Though you're bound to be mobbed by
fans hungry for more Saint Philia,
so maybe that's not the best idea...
A walk?
Gardening!
Gardening?
I hear fishing is nice, too!
Fishing?
Well, what about reading?
Ah, I do read often.
I decipher ancient texts
and study scientific textbooks.
I love reading, too!
Romance novels are my favorite!
Romance novels?
Ro-manse-no-vells?
Wait, you don't know what
romance novels are?!
Well, I haven't read any,
but I do know about them.
They're psychological profiles of couples
engaged in mutual affection, correct?
That somehow feels so close and so far...
Say, are you not at all interested
in romance yourself?
I suppose not.
But you're so beautiful!
It's more that I've never had the chance...
In that case, I'll lend you some
of my favorite romance novels!
I'll bring you my very favorite,
so I hope you'll tell me what you think!
Yes, I'll be eager to read it.
Things sound lively in here.
Your Highness! Welcome!
I was hoping to discuss something
with you, Miss Philia.
Before I get to the matter at hand,
I feel I owe you an explanation.
It's about the fight my brother
and I had over bringing you here.
Yes, I recall he mentioned it at the church.
You shouldn't let it bother—
It does bother me, though!
It isn't that I didn't want you
to come here or anything.
But as I told you before,
I was against the idea of buying
a saint like some sort of commodity.
My brother was already
on edge for other reasons,
and we both lost our cool...
To be honest, I still think
it's wrong to buy someone.
I never want to do that again.
But I'm still glad I met you.
Those are my genuine feelings.
I wanted to make that clear
so there would be no misunderstanding.
I understand.
Oh my!
Pardon, Your Highness. What did
you want to discuss with her?
Leonardo, not the time!
Oh, that's right!
Miss Philia, I've been wanting to ask you...
Would you like to try being a tutor?
I think it's wonderful!
But I'm not sure if I can
be an effective mentor.
You're so great at teaching, though!
When I ask about your duties, you always
give such easy-to-understand explanations!
Besides, I'm sure a saint-in-training
would make a great companion for you.
He said she's younger than you,
but I bet it won't be by much.
Saint Philia?
I'm sorry. I was thinking of my sister.
I sent her a letter,
but I've received no reply.
I'll check to make sure
the messenger did his job.
Now here you are, Saint Philia!
Help yourself to dinner!
It's very good.
What?
Sorry, we're just delighted
to hear you say that you like it!
Oh? Could it be you haven't realized?
In the past, you always ate in silence,
but lately you've been
telling us how you feel!
I'm sure it makes all Leonardo's
work feel more worthwhile, too!
I've endeavored to expand my repertoire.
What do you mean?
Can you believe it? Leonardo's been
the one cooking your meals recently!
Just a hobby.
You always cook this delicious food for me?
We aren't the only ones contributing.
Everything on this table, from the vegetables
to the fruit, meat, and eggs,
was sent to us by the people out
of gratitude for what you've done.
Even the flowers!
It almost feels like we're
dining with the whole kingdom, huh?
I always think food tastes better
when you eat with someone else!
I see. I had no idea.
Exchanging books with someone,
the improvement of a meal with company...
I've long been alone,
so these are things I've never known.
Saint Philia?
Leonardo. Lena.
Thank you very much.
It's quite delicious.
How is it, Mia?
Oh, it's just delicious!
It is, isn't it?!
I brought in the finest
ingredients just for you!
Once we're wed, you'll be able
to feast like this every day!
Oh, you're just so dainty and precious!
Saint Philia! Excuse me!
Lena? What's the matter?
I wanted to give it to you straight away!
It's a letter from the Kingdom of Girtonia,
sent by Mia Adenauer!
What?
What does this mean?
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
The letter you sent never
reached her, you say?
Indeed.
Mia says she's written to me
because she hasn't heard from me.
But Parnacorta's royal messenger assured
me he delivered it to the Adenauer estate.
My parents must have destroyed it
before it reached Mia's hands.
I believe they may want to cut
off contact between the two of us.
That's awful...
It is upsetting.
Saint Philia, you'd like a way to ensure
your letters reach Saint Mia, yes?
I do, but...
In that case, I think we can get it done!
What?
Are you present, Himari?
Yes.
I am here.
Allow me to make introductions.
This is Himari.
She is another member of your personal
guard assigned by the royal family.
A real shock, right?
Himari has been at your side all this time!
What? Since when?
Since the day you arrived.
I had no idea.
Your surprise is understandable.
That's right!
Because you see, Himari is...
a ninja!
A ninja?
I've heard of those.
They are warriors from the island kingdom
of Murasame to the northeast
who specialize in stealth and reconnaissance.
Himari, I'm sure you've been listening in.
Can you take a letter directly to Saint Mia?
Of course.
On the name of the Fuuma clan.
To enter Girtonia now will require
traversing forests swarming with monsters.
The people trying to keep Mia and I
apart may also attempt to hinder you.
Himari?
Saint Philia, you may issue me
the order without reservation.
From the shadows, I have witnessed
your attempts to save this kingdom.
For you, I am prepared to risk my life.
In that case, Himari...
Yes?
Will you take a letter to my sister, Mia?
Be prudent, of course.
If you're at risk of discovery,
don't hesitate to flee.
But...
If it seems...
If it seems like it might
be possible, then please...
Continue.
Please protect my sister.
If it seems likely something will befall
her, take her with you and run.
Very well.
It shall be done.
That's the final pillar.
Now, once I get the barrier up...
Amazing work, Saint Mia!
You complete rituals even
faster than Saint Philia!
You're filling in for her like it's nothing!
We'd gladly give our lives to protect
a saint as wonderful as you!
They make it sound easy.
Absurd.
It's true that I'm faster
with rituals than my sister...
But that's all.
My barriers are far more fragile than hers.
Were a large number
of monsters to spawn at once,
they would shatter it.
To prevent that, I'm forced
to forge additional layers of barrier.
And that consequently takes longer.
They have no idea...
Saint Mia!
Monsters!
A ton of them!
No! How could I not
have noticed them closing in?!
They're gonna kill us!
Leave this to me!
Saint Mia!
Get back!
Silver...
Judgment!
I knew it. Something's not right here.
Silver Judgment!
I'm not sure who's guarding whom...
Saint Mia, are you all right?
Y-Yes...
It appears the monsters
are vanquished for now.
Please use this.
Thank you very much.
What a considerate young man.
This handwriting...
Please—
Is my sister well?
You have no need to worry.
My mistress, Lady Philia,
is doing well in Parnacorta.
We are most indebted to Saint Philia,
but our affection for her
goes even beyond that,
so we wish to assist her in any way we can.
That is why I was sent.
I'm so glad!
My sister is with people who care about her!
You've found some wonderful
company, Big Sister.
Saint Mia! Are you all right?!
W-Wait!
I'll leave my door unlocked this evening.
Could we talk a little bit longer?
Including about this letter.
Very well.
I shall speak with you later.
Okay!
Himari, reporting as promised.
I certainly didn't expect you
to jump down from the ceiling.
It was a necessary measure
to elude the guards.
Forgive me.
I-I see...
So you're a lady, are you?
The art of disguise is a crucial
skill for going undetected.
Have you read the letter?
Yes, many times!
Thank you, Himari.
I now understand the threat
facing our kingdom.
Saint Philia says it is a race against time.
She went and did that ancient ritual, did she?
Wish I coulda seen it!
It was truly a splendid sight.
It's not something I could pull off, though.
So I'll have to muster
all the kingdom's forces, will I?
I'm afraid that won't be easy.
Saint Philia was concerned
about that as well.
It's just... that louse of a prince
is the one in charge right now.
He only cares about himself.
Please, my sister...
Would you like to escape?
I could easily take one person to Parnacorta.
Saint Philia is worried about you as well.
This is your chance to get to safety.
Come with me.
If I take her hand, I get to see my sister?
What reason do I have to stay here...
in this kingdom that scorned
and exiled my sister?
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside by
My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom.
Next time, episode 5:
Next Time
Episode 5
"Golden Freesia"
"Golden Freesia."